Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 17
  - Ringleb: "Minimum take-off distance with rocket assist,", October 1943 (Box-folder 17: 21)
  - Stender: "Observation on yawing oscillations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 22)
  - Wieselberger: "On the influence of wind tunnel boundaries upon the drag especially in the regions of compressible flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 23)
  - Schiller: "Oscillations of flat rectangular plates in subsonic flow. Continuation.,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 24)
  - Palitzsch: "Preliminary investigation of KF 122 jet bomber in a 10 ft. wind tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 25)
  - Puffert: "Preliminary report on high velocity tests of swept wings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 26)
  - Novotny: "Rectangular wing with fixed slat and fairing over slot,", February 1944 (Box-folder 17: 27)
  - Schwier: "Research on suction and blowing performed outside of Gottingen,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 28)
  - Wehrse: "Sectionally shaped cover-plates for built-up steel spars for FW 190 fighter,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 29)
  - Busch-Jaeger: "Specifications for aircraft terminal boards,", February 1945 (Box-folder 17: 30)
  - Wehrse & Heintzelmann: "Steel spars for the Fw-300A bomber,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 31)
  - Schroedter: "Tables for determination of the critical Mach number,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 32)
  - Dietz and Harling: "Tail wheel flutter,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 33)
  - Heise: "Testing of a new roller slat-drive,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 34)
  - Riegels & Brand: Transparencies for a paper with missing title, circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 35)
  - "Uniform designation of airplane parts,", 5 August 1949 (Box-folder 17: 36)
  - Holbig & Weber: "Wind tunnel tests on a model of a 7.5 cm grenade HL 43,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 37)
  - Partial document missing first 15 pages, circa 1945 (Box-folder 17: 38)
- Box 18
  - Roeber: "3-component measurements on a nacelle,", May 1940 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Strassl: "3-component tests on short cylinders at supersonic velocities,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Weber & Höckner: "3-component tests on the device "Kurt" in the supersonic wind tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Puffert: "3-component wind tunnel tests on swept wings, and on a complete model with swept wings,", 7 July 1942 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Hansen: "6-component tests on a flap-wing with great dihedral position and sweep,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Helmbold: "A few results of aerodynamic industrial research,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Reichardt: "Cavitation installations for small cavitation numbers,", 12 February 1946 (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - "Cavitation testing,", August 1945 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Reichardt: "Cavitation tests on Henschel bodies,", 12 July 1945 (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - "Circuit diagrams of the Me-262 electrical systems,", September 1944 (Box-folder 18: 10)
  - Reichardt: "Concerning cavitation installations for small cavitation numbers,", 12 February 1945 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Hütter: "Development work at Hütter,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Klüglich: "Example for the calculation of a two stage supercharger,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Schiller: "Experimental determination of the damping coefficient of flat plates vibrating in subsonic flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - Walz: "Experiments with removal of friction layer by suction on a wing profile NACA 23015 with different positions of the suction slots along the cord,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 15)
  - Lemme: "Force tests and pressure distributions on a wing with bent nose, slat, camber - and extension flap,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 16)
  - Nüll: "Investigation of the air compressor of B. Thomas,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 17)
  - Werner Pfenninger: "Investigations on friction decrease of airfoils, especially by means of boundary layer bleeding by suction,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 18)
  - Eisenmann: "Lateral stability of an airplane with a swept-back wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 19)
  - Horn, Voigt, and Ogau: "Me 262 with 2x Jumo-Sonder driving gear,", 8 October 1943 (Box-folder 18: 20)
  - Schwenk: "Measurements for a tapered swept-back wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 21)
  - Eggink: "On shock waves with separated flow,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 22)
  - Oswatitsch: "Pressure recovery for missiles with reaction propulsion at high supersonic speeds. (The efficiency of shock diffusers),", circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 23)
  - Küch: "Safety glass and transparent plastics for high altitude aircraft,", 9 March 1938 (Box-folder 18: 24)
  - von Vistinghoff & Scheel: "Test report on the investigation of flow about two turbine blade profiles by the aid of the interference method,", 31 May 1944 (Box-folder 18: 25)
  - Partial report missing title page, circa 1945 (Box-folder 18: 26)
- Box 19
  - Hansen: "6-component tests on a flap-wing with great dihedral position and sweep,", 20 January 1944 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Neuman: "A simple approximation method for the determination of the damping constant R for linearly damped oscillations with arbitrary restoring terms,", 19 May 1943 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Merves: "Aerodynamic data for lateral stability investigations,", 1941 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Böhm: "Air forces and flow phenomena on propelled projectiles,", August 1944 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Multhopp: "Der pfeilflügel bei hohen Fluggeschwindigkeiten,", 7 October 1941 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Fitjer: "Die erprobung der flugzeugräder und -reifen und die sich daraus ergebenden forderungen,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - "Directions for using the FBM hard chromium plating baths,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Hoerner: "Drag of external tanks,", 17 March 1945 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Kress: "Economical manufacturing accuracies,", July 1938 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Maier & Renz: "Flutter tests on dual wheels,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Blasberg: "Hard chromium plating equipment for treating cylinders,", 3 December 1943 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - Mewes: "Investigations of lateral motions of aircraft,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - Heintzelmann: "Main spar-flange of the Fw 300 A with 1620, under refining treatment to 120 kg/nm2,", July 1943 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - Hobusch: "Punktgeschweißte Stahlholme,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - Schwier: "Tests on drag changes of an airfoil in blowing out heated air,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - "Tests with Intava anti-icing compound 1429,", 2 February 1939 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Küch: "Transparent synthetic materials for the glazing of aircraft (a section of the report: Synthetic materials and the use in aircraft construction),", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 17)
  - Junge: "Turbulence tests in the higher atmosphere layers,", March 1938 (Box-folder 19: 18)
  - Goettingen: "Wind tunnel tests on various wing profiles,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 19: 19)
  - "Working directions for the chromium plating of exhaust valves 9-801.311-770.12,", 10 October 1942 (Box-folder 19: 20)
- Box 20
  - Theil: "Effect of the glide ratio on the range,", 21 August 1941 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Gebelein: "Evaluation of a cinetheodolitically measured trajectory in order to obtain velocities, accelerations and coefficients of aerodynamic forces,", 19 March 1945 (Box-folder 20: 2)
  - Grammel: "Excerpts from the book "The Theory of the Gyroscope,", 21 June 1948 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Tollmien: "Formation of envelopes of Mach waves on a tangentially struck blade,", May 1943 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Gottwald: "Investigations of bearing devices with small friction,", March 1940 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Heller: "Investigations on the constancy of the thrust,", 1 September 1940 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Army Research Center: "Investigations on the constancy of the thrust II,", 18 January 1941 (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - Boering: "Measurements on marginal vortices on wing models at the Aerodynamic Institute at Warsaw,", December 1942 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Handel & Sjoden: "Method of increasing range by means of frequency modulation of impulses,", 21 November 1947 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Heugartner: "Most favorable angle of divergence of a laval nozzle,", 31 August 1940 (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - Oswatitsch: "The pressure recovery of projectiles with jet propulsion at supersonic speeds (The efficiency of thrust diffusors),", January 1944 (Box-folder 20: 11)
  - Wegener: "Research reports of the hydraulics testing laboratories,", 20 March 1945 (Box-folder 20: 12)
  - Hemesath: "Sealing material (Dichtwerkstoffe),", May 1943 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Graf: "Sensitivity of homogeneous alloys to stress corrosion,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Werminghoff: "Study of heat exchanger,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Eberan: "The tests on the HAP-WA 3048 B were conducted during the period of March 19, 1942, to April 25, 1942, by the Automotive Insitute of the Technical College, Dresden, Germany," (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - "Untersuchungen am Wärmeaustauscher,", 14 July 1942 (Box-folder 20: 17)
- Box 21
  - Kosel: "Committee meeting on production of steel spars,", February 1943 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Lindemann: "Comparisons of results of tests on different aircraft models in the DVL high velocity wind tunnel,", 1944 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Gothert & Kawalki: "Compressible flow about various flat profiles near sonic velocity,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - Kautter: "Decimeter wave technique,", December 1943 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Wieghardt: "Erhöhung des turbulenten reibungswiderstandes durch oberflächenstörungen,", 1943 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Thum & Wunderlich: "Fretting corrosion on closely fitting surfaces and its significance for the fatigue fracture,", December 1935 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Gottwald: "Investigation of bearings having little friction,", December 1941 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Schmidt: "Investigation of exhaust steam nozzles,", 20 November 1942 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Gottwald: "Investigation on bearings with small friction,", 1940 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Theil & Weissinger: "Maximum lift determinations on a 35 degree swept-back trapeze wing with various landing aids,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Dollhopf & Schmidt: "Most favorable dimensions of a laval nozzle with external pressure changing with time,", 8 April 1940 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Vettin: "On the integration of non-linear differential equations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Heinz: "Pressure distribution on the solid of revolution WK 581 E at the mach number M = 8.00 in which the formation of vortices has been taken into account,", 7 December 1943 (Box-folder 21: 13)
  - Doetsch: "Results of the profile research of the German Research Institute for Aeronautics,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Kaul: "Statistische erhebungen über betriebsbeanspruchungen von flugzeugflügeln,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Messerschmidt: "Temperature measurements on wooden fuselage models with turbo-jet engines,", 1 April 1948 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Vueller & Knobloch: "Test results on aerial missiles in the sonic range of speed,", 23 November 1944 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Guérard: "Theorie und anwendung con rechentafeln für zweigurtige holme,", 12 October 1944 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - Jehle: "Untersuchungen über das Tragwergewicht der Baumuster Ju 87 und Ju 88,", 25 July 1939 (Box-folder 21: 19)
- Box 22
  - Roehm: "Aerial gunnery,", August 1942 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Kurzweg: "The aerodynamic development of the anti-aircraft rocket "Wasserfall" ("Cataract"),", January 1946 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Oswatitch & Böhm: "Aerodynamic forces and flow phenomena of driven missiles,", August 1944 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Herrmann: "Calculation of the trajectory of the missile A III with cross wind,", 18 January 1938 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Lippisch: "Climb of rocket-propelled aircraft,", September 1941 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Lindemann: "Comparisons of results of tests on different aircraft models in the DVL high velocity wind tunnel,", 1944 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Kretschmer: "Construction methods for stabilizers and control surfaces,", 28 November 1941 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Pabst: "The diffusion of hot gas jets in flowing air,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Göthert: "High speed measurements on a swept-back wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Cornelius & Santleben: "Investigation of spot welding varnish,", October 1943 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Jacker: "Investigations on glazing materials for altitude chambers,", 1942 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Stein: ""Moeve" Project. Calculated results on the controllability of aircraft using the jet method for increasing lift,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Heybey: "The normal compression shock,", 8 May 1940 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Reichardt: "On the determination of favourable shapes of bodies for high speed by cavitation tests,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Mehlhardt: "Safety of aircraft against uninsulated electrical parts,", December 1937 (Box-folder 22: 15)
  - Schelp: "Survey of special engine development in Germany,", 25 May 1945 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - Fricke: "Theory of lead for moving aircraft guns,", 29 June 1944 (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Schmid: "Ultra-high-frequency sight unit,", 1945 (Box-folder 22: 18)
  - Kautter: "Ultrahigh frequency techniques,", December 1943 (Box-folder 22: 19)
  - "Wind tunnel tests on various wing profiles,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 22: 20)
- Box 23
  - Heybey: "The applicability of an approximation expression derived by Prof. Tollmien in the First Research Report,", 19 January 1940 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Heybey: "Average errors of the three-component measurements due to uncertain readings of the measuring instruments,", 28 November 1941 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Sissingh: "Ceiling of the helicopter,", 15 December 1943 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Hauk: "The effect of incremental hardness of weld spots upon the strength of spotwelds in high-strength steel sheets,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Bader: "The flight characteristics of German airplanes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Weissinger: "Forces and moments of a wing in yaw,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - "German aeronautical symbols & notations,", December 1937 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Zobel: "High speed tunnel of the Aeronautical Research Institute - Hermann Goerring Brunswick,", 1943 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Zobel: "High speed tunnel of the Aeronautical Research Institute - Hermann Goerring Brunswick,", 1943 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - "Investigation of aileron effectiveness of a sweptback wing and a "blunted" sweptback wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Winkler: "A novel product planimeter,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Wegener: "Observations on the S-shape of the steering control curves of missile "Wasserfall",", 3 March 1945 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Benzinger: "Physiological basis for the construction and use of stratosphere airplanes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Prochazka, Möonsmühl: "Report on radio disturbances from jet propulsion,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Lehnert: "Report on three-component tests on the glider models A4 V12/a & A4 V12/o,", 27 November 1940 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Schrenk: "Research on boundary layer control at the Göttingen Institute of Aerodynamics,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - Gaedke: "Sight specifications for aircraft armament,", 1942 (Box-folder 23: 17)
  - Trau: "Spectral distribution of the internal photo-electric effect in lead sulfide and its long wave limit,", October 1943 (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - Theil, Klingelhöffer & Zech: "Two-dimensional uncontrolled trajectory of a model aggregate affected by the wind,", February 1940 (Box-folder 23: 19)
- Box 24
  - Ritter: "3-component tests on Feuerlilie F-25, in the 2.8 m. dia. high velocity tunnel of the LFA,", 12 January 1944 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Thiel: "5th report on gliders. (New proposition for calculation of mean flight paths of gliders),", 19 December 1941 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Thiel & Weissinger: "6-component testson a 35 degree back swept trapeze wing with and without extension flaps,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Thiel: "6th report on gliders. Influence of wing-area F on flight-range X.,", 4 February 1942 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Schrenk: "Aerodynamic design problems of Gottinger suction aircraft,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Heybey: "The behavior of normal compression shocks in a laval nozzle,", 14 October 1942 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Mangler: "Boundary layers with symmetrical airflow about bodies of revolution,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Kochel: "Density measurements to determine the structure of compression shocks on wedges,", 13 July 1945 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Erdmann: "Drag coefficients of the A 4 V 1 P including jet and friction effects for sub and supersonic velocities. Investigation of jet expansion,", 24 March 1943 (Box-folder 24: 9)
  - Pabst: "Drag of bodies of revolution at varying mach numbers - critical comparison of the various measurements,", March 1945 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Eber: "Experimental research on friction temperature and heat transfer for simple bodies at supersonic velocities,", November 1941 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Jordan: "Four years of flutter research,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - "Fundamental aerodynamic investigations for development of arrow-stabilized projectiles,", 4 February 1943 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Goethert: "High velocity measurements on bodies of revolution,", May 1944 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Pfleghaar: "Investigation of a one-tube firing chamber under different operating conditions in the DVL test stand, pt. III,", 12 March 1946 (Box-folder 24: 15)
  - Hoh: "Investigations on the propagation of spark sound waves in the wind tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 16)
  - Schwier: "Lift increase by blowing out air; tests on airfoil of 12% thickness, using various types of flap,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 17)
  - Leist & Meyer: "Light metal soldering,", April 1943 (Box-folder 24: 18)
  - Riegels & Betz: "M.A.P Völkenrode,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 19)
  - Weber: "On Betz's computation of the diffuser losses,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 20)
  - Hartwig: "Pressure distribution measurements over a cross-section of an air intake located near the leading edge at the wing root,", 7 July 1944 (Box-folder 24: 21)
  - Wockner: "Principles of design of suction airships and preliminary flight operations,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 22)
  - Wolff: "Proposals for all-weather and night-fighters,", 22 March 1945 (Box-folder 24: 23)
  - Matossi & Passoth: "Pyroelectric investigations,", 10 September 1944 (Box-folder 24: 24)
  - Horten Bros: "Stability considerations on swept wings,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 25)
  - Walchner: "Systematic missile measurements in a wind-tunnel,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 26)
  - Kappus: "The tailless construction of the turbo-jet fightrer compared to the standard model,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 27)
  - Horten Bros: "Ten years development on the "wing only" high speed fighter airplane,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 28)
  - Ludwieg: "Wind tunnel measurements on ducted projectiles,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 24: 29)
- Box 25
  - Kurzweg: "Aerodynamic development of the missile "Taifun",", 5 March 1945 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Schuler & Fuchs: "Automatic control of airplanes with special regard to yaw,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Lutz: "Bases of comparison of jet propulsion units,", Februrary 1940 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Hermann: "Brief report on the development, scope and operational setup of the Wasserbau Versuchsanstalt Kochelsee Inc.,", 20 May 1945 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Schmidt: "Cannons with electromagnetic acceleration of projectiles,", August 1944 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Oehmichen: "De-foaming of oil,", December 1942 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Daeves: "The development of heat and scale-resisting metals on the addition of high heat-resisting ceramic materials,", December 1943 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Zurmuchl: "Drag coefficient tables,", May 1943 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Pabst: "Drag of bodies of revolution at varying mach numbers - critical comparison of the various measurements,", March 1945 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Arado: "E-395 superspeed bomber with 4 HE 109011 A engines,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Grünewald: "The effectiveness of the cooling phase control valve of the drying equipment of the 40x40 cm wind tunnel,", 11 September 1945 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Fahrenhorst: "Experimental Extrusion Press,", October 1943 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Eber: "Experimental resesarch on friction temperature and heat transfer for simple bodies at supersonic velocities,", November 1941 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Grünewald and Kraus: "Experimental study of shock formation on cones,", 13 April 1944 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Eckert: "Hinge moments and control effectiveness of "Wasserfall" control surface 21,", December 1944 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Brennecke: "Increasing the lift of a swept-back wing,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 16)
  - Schugt: "New method and equipment for continuously tracking a flying target with 3 bearing axes,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 17)
  - Pfister: "On the reflection of ultra-short waves from clouds,", 20 January 1945 (Box-folder 25: 18)
  - Peucker: "Optical ultra-red proximity fuze,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 19)
  - Wegener: "Preliminary results derived form oscillation measurements in the wind tunnel of the jet model of missile C2/E2a of project "Wasserfall",", 9 August 1944 (Box-folder 25: 20)
  - Hullman & Wendland: "Pressurized cabins of FW190 and TA 152 H,", 10 October 1943 (Box-folder 25: 21)
  - Kotthoff: "Pulse jammer mesched II,", October 1943 (Box-folder 25: 22)
  - "Radio direction finder, 118F,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 23)
  - Schacky: "Range curves of ground aircraft reporting radar,", 11 October 1944 (Box-folder 25: 24)
  - Kraus: "Report on the numerical and graphical determination of transient temperature distributions in an insulating layer,", November 1943 (Box-folder 25: 25)
  - Lehnert: "Report on three-component measurements on the winged shell A4 V13/e,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 26)
  - Schwier: "Research on suction and blowing performed outside of Gottingen,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 27)
  - Schaefer: "Safety devices for nuts and bolts,", April 1944 (Box-folder 25: 28)
  - Pretsch: "The stability of twodimensional laminar flow with pressure drop and pressure rise,", 1941 (Box-folder 25: 29)
  - Wegener: "The taking and evaluation of oscillograms of oscillating bodies in the wind tunnel,", 16 September 1944 (Box-folder 25: 30)
  - Zobel: "Tests of rectangular wings of HE 177 with and without skin wrinkles made in the 2.8 m high velocity wind tunnel of L.F.A.,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 31)
  - Regenscheit: "Tests on high lift of suction-type wings with flaps,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 32)
  - Telefunken: "Zielflug-peilanlage,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 25: 33)
- Box 26
  - Denkoehler: "A graphic method for obtaining directional characterstics of linearly arranged receiver arrays,", August 1944 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Billing: "Acoustic direction indicator,", March 1944 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Lutze: "Circuit for decimeter waves with phase velocities greater than or less than light velocity,", September 1942 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Lechner: "Electrical measurements of the flight path of a missile or aircraft,", February 1940 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Schwede: "Field-intensity transformer,", May 1939 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Klingehoeffer & Schnitzler: "Investigation of precipitation-static phenomena,", January 1940 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Meagher, Giaccone, & Sosnoski: "High performance fuel detonation tests in an R-2800-34 engine - effect of exhaust pressure,", August 1946 (Box-folder 26: 7)